

# Oksana Melnyk Frontend Developer,

Wiesbaden, Germany / remote

I am a frontend developer with one year of experience and a background in Sales Management. I specialize in creating responsive, user-friendly applications while bringing positive energy to the team as a collaborative player dedicated to achieving our goals. My proficiency includes HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript, React.js.

EXPERIENCE -

# Frontend Developer

Freelance

Present - 07.2023, remote

• Build a landing page, directly collaborated with Client, launch of a website

## **Wordpress Developer**

Freelance

2023 - 2021, remote

- Build web sites from design to implementation,
- Directly collaborated with Client, actively giving suggestions for an improvement of UI and UX experience

#### Sales Manager

Cooverbox, premium packaging company

2023 - 2021, remote

- Comunication with Product Owner, marketing specialists, designers
- Directly collaborated with Client, actively giving suggestions for an improvement of UI and UX experience

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

#### Front-end development course

**Beetroot Academy** 

08.2023 - 04.2023, online

#### Front-end development course

**Beetroot Academy** 

08.2023 - 04.2023, online

EDUCATION

## **Management and Business Administration**

National University of Oil and Gas

2012 - 2009, Ivano-Frankivsk (Ukraine)

CONTACTS

Website Portfolio

oks.melnuk@gmail.com

+49 176 67 445 802

LinkedIn

<u>GitHub</u>

SKILLS

### **Technologies**

HTML CSS/CSS3 SASS/SCSS JavaScript (ES6+)

React Bootstrap BEM Git GitHub

#### **Tools**

Visual Studio Code Figma, Adobe Photoshop/ Illustrator

#### Languages

English (intermediate)
German (B2 level in progress)
Ukrainian (native)

**PROJECTS** 

#### Finmill, landing page

Demo Code

EventUp, website

Demo Code

Ikea clone, API

Demo Code

Rick&Morty (React, API)

Demo Code

**Shopping Cart, JS** 

Demo Code